{
    "subject": "resource/Famous_Studios",
    "predicate": "ontology/keyPerson",
    "object": "resource/Dan_Gordon_(animator)",
    "human_readable": "Dan Gordon is a key person at Famous Studios.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9260417222976685,
            "question": "What role does Dan Gordon play at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8966114521026611,
            "question": "What are some of the projects that Dan Gordon has been involved in at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8354339599609375,
            "question": "How long has Dan Gordon been working at Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8229482769966125,
            "question": "Has Dan Gordon worked at other companies besides Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7584131956100464,
            "question": "Who is Dan Gordon?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5654962658882141,
            "question": "What is Famous Studios known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3912413716316223,
            "question": "What kind of company is Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37943053245544434,
            "question": "Are there any other notable figures associated with Famous Studios?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3092292249202728,
            "question": "What are some of the successes that Famous Studios has achieved?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2781718075275421,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Dan Gordon's background or education?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dan Gordon is a key person at Famous Studios.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7298_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the successes that Famous Studios has achieved?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7298_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other notable figures associated with Famous Studios?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7298_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of company is Famous Studios?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7298_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7298_70.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I found that:\n\n* The documents mention Dan Gordon as a storyboard artist and film director who worked at Famous Studios, Hanna-Barbera Productions, and other studios. He is also mentioned as one of the supervisors (credited on screen as \"directors\") at Famous Studios.\n* There are several mentions of Dan Gordon's work at Famous Studios, including his involvement in the production of cartoons such as Popeye Happy Birthdaze and You're a Sap, Mr. Jap.\n\nBased on this information, I can conclude that:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Dan Gordon is a key person at Famous Studios.\" The relevant details can be found in multiple files, indicating his involvement as both a writer and director for the studio."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}